[
    {
        "nodeID": 10,
        "children": [
            {
                "nodeID": 6,
                "children": [
                    {
                        "nodeID": 4,
                        "children": [
                            {
                                "nodeID": 2,
                                "children": [
                                    {
                                        "nodeID": 0,
                                        "children": [],
                                        "question": "Since you are mutating the state, and you expect a render to take place, please check the location of the state update for any potential bugs in the implementation",
                                        "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                                        "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                                        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                                        "infoDesc": "Render call expected"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "nodeID": 1,
                                        "children": [],
                                        "question": "Since you are mutating the state and you do not expect a render to take place, consider removing the state update call to resolve the bug",
                                        "thisAnswer": "No",
                                        "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                                        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                                        "infoDesc": "Render call not expected"
                                    }
                                ],
                                "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
                                "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                                "nodeType": "question",
                                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                                "infoDesc": "Component mutates state"
                            },
                            {
                                "nodeID": 3,
                                "children": [],
                                "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
                                "thisAnswer": "No",
                                "nodeType": "question",
                                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                                "infoDesc": "Component does not mutates state"
                            }
                        ],
                        "question": "Is this component mutating the state?",
                        "thisAnswer": "Function",
                        "nodeType": "question",
                        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html",
                        "infoDesc": "Component Type: Function"
                    },
                    {
                        "nodeID": 5,
                        "children": [],
                        "question": "Is this component mutating the state?",
                        "thisAnswer": "Class",
                        "nodeType": "question",
                        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html",
                        "infoDesc": "Component Type: Class"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is the bug in a function component or a class component?",
                "thisAnswer": "React",
                "nodeType": "question",
                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/components-and-props.html#function-and-class-components",
                "infoDesc": "Framework used: React"
            },
            {
                "nodeID": 7,
                "children": [],
                "question": "This is not supported yet",
                "thisAnswer": "Angular",
                "nodeType": "question",
                "infoLink": null,
                "infoDesc": "Framework used: Angular"
            },
            {
                "nodeID": 8,
                "children": [],
                "question": "This is not supported yet",
                "thisAnswer": "Vue.js",
                "nodeType": "question",
                "infoLink": null,
                "infoDesc": "Framework used: Vue.js"
            },
            {
                "nodeID": 9,
                "children": [],
                "question": "This is not supported yet",
                "thisAnswer": "Gatsby.js",
                "nodeType": "question",
                "infoLink": null,
                "infoDesc": "Framework used: Gatsby.js"
            }
        ],
        "question": "What framework or technology is being used?",
        "thisAnswer": null,
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_framework",
        "infoDesc": null
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 6,
        "children": [
            {
                "nodeID": 4,
                "children": [
                    {
                        "nodeID": 2,
                        "children": [
                            {
                                "nodeID": 0,
                                "children": [],
                                "question": "Since you are mutating the state, and you expect a render to take place, please check the location of the state update for any potential bugs in the implementation",
                                "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                                "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                                "infoDesc": "Render call expected"
                            },
                            {
                                "nodeID": 1,
                                "children": [],
                                "question": "Since you are mutating the state and you do not expect a render to take place, consider removing the state update call to resolve the bug",
                                "thisAnswer": "No",
                                "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                                "infoDesc": "Render call not expected"
                            }
                        ],
                        "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
                        "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                        "nodeType": "question",
                        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                        "infoDesc": "Component mutates state"
                    },
                    {
                        "nodeID": 3,
                        "children": [],
                        "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
                        "thisAnswer": "No",
                        "nodeType": "question",
                        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                        "infoDesc": "Component does not mutates state"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is this component mutating the state?",
                "thisAnswer": "Function",
                "nodeType": "question",
                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html",
                "infoDesc": "Component Type: Function"
            },
            {
                "nodeID": 5,
                "children": [],
                "question": "Is this component mutating the state?",
                "thisAnswer": "Class",
                "nodeType": "question",
                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html",
                "infoDesc": "Component Type: Class"
            }
        ],
        "question": "Is the bug in a function component or a class component?",
        "thisAnswer": "React",
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/components-and-props.html#function-and-class-components",
        "infoDesc": "Framework used: React"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 4,
        "children": [
            {
                "nodeID": 2,
                "children": [
                    {
                        "nodeID": 0,
                        "children": [],
                        "question": "Since you are mutating the state, and you expect a render to take place, please check the location of the state update for any potential bugs in the implementation",
                        "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                        "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                        "infoDesc": "Render call expected"
                    },
                    {
                        "nodeID": 1,
                        "children": [],
                        "question": "Since you are mutating the state and you do not expect a render to take place, consider removing the state update call to resolve the bug",
                        "thisAnswer": "No",
                        "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                        "infoDesc": "Render call not expected"
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
                "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                "nodeType": "question",
                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                "infoDesc": "Component mutates state"
            },
            {
                "nodeID": 3,
                "children": [],
                "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
                "thisAnswer": "No",
                "nodeType": "question",
                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                "infoDesc": "Component does not mutates state"
            }
        ],
        "question": "Is this component mutating the state?",
        "thisAnswer": "Function",
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html",
        "infoDesc": "Component Type: Function"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 2,
        "children": [
            {
                "nodeID": 0,
                "children": [],
                "question": "Since you are mutating the state, and you expect a render to take place, please check the location of the state update for any potential bugs in the implementation",
                "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                "infoDesc": "Render call expected"
            },
            {
                "nodeID": 1,
                "children": [],
                "question": "Since you are mutating the state and you do not expect a render to take place, consider removing the state update call to resolve the bug",
                "thisAnswer": "No",
                "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                "infoDesc": "Render call not expected"
            }
        ],
        "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
        "thisAnswer": "Yes",
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
        "infoDesc": "Component mutates state"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 0,
        "children": [],
        "question": "Since you are mutating the state, and you expect a render to take place, please check the location of the state update for any potential bugs in the implementation",
        "thisAnswer": "Yes",
        "nodeType": "hypothesis",
        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
        "infoDesc": "Render call expected"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 1,
        "children": [],
        "question": "Since you are mutating the state and you do not expect a render to take place, consider removing the state update call to resolve the bug",
        "thisAnswer": "No",
        "nodeType": "hypothesis",
        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
        "infoDesc": "Render call not expected"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 3,
        "children": [],
        "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
        "thisAnswer": "No",
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
        "infoDesc": "Component does not mutates state"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 5,
        "children": [],
        "question": "Is this component mutating the state?",
        "thisAnswer": "Class",
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html",
        "infoDesc": "Component Type: Class"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 7,
        "children": [],
        "question": "This is not supported yet",
        "thisAnswer": "Angular",
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": null,
        "infoDesc": "Framework used: Angular"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 8,
        "children": [],
        "question": "This is not supported yet",
        "thisAnswer": "Vue.js",
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": null,
        "infoDesc": "Framework used: Vue.js"
    },
    {
        "nodeID": 9,
        "children": [],
        "question": "This is not supported yet",
        "thisAnswer": "Gatsby.js",
        "nodeType": "question",
        "infoLink": null,
        "infoDesc": "Framework used: Gatsby.js"
    }
]